Why you want to become a scary king,
(ﾆｰﾅ･ﾄﾞﾗﾝｺﾞ)あなたが なんで
怖い王様になろうとするのか➡
それは分からない｡
that I don't know.
けど 私は あなたのことを…｡
But, how I feel about you...
I want to help you with whatever
you're dealing with.
あなたが抱えているものを
一緒に背負いたい｡
I'm back!
たっだいま～！
-You idiot!
-Say what now?
はい？
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)こんな時間まで➡
Just where have you been all this time?
どこ ほっつき歩いてんだ！
ごめ～ん！
Sorry.
(ﾘﾀ)あなた まさか
竜になったんじゃないでしょうね？
You didn't turn into a dragon, did you?
へっ？
そ… そんなわけないじゃん｡
Of course not. Well, I'm off to bed.
私 もう寝ま～す！
ふふふっ｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)怪しいですね｡
She sure is acting fishy.
(ﾘﾀ)まったく
アフロは何をしてたのよ｡
What in the world was Afro doing?
うふふっ｡
≫(ﾌｧﾊﾞﾛ･ﾚｵｰﾈ)ニーナ｡
Nina.
えっ？ あっ なんだ 師匠か｡
Oh, it's just you, Master.
驚かさないでよ｡
Don't startle me like that.
はぁ～｡ 厄介な男に
ほれちまったみてぇだな｡
Looks like you fell for a guy who's real trouble.
えっ？
シャリオスに会ってたんだろ｡
You met with Charioce, right?
な… 何言ってんの 師匠｡
そんなわけ ないない！
What are you talking about, Master?
Of course I didn't.
ふん｡ そっか そうだよな➡
I see.
You're right.
お前みたいなちんちくりんに
王様が引っ掛かるわけねぇよなぁ｡
There's no way a little shrimp like you
could hook a king.
そ… そうだよ 師匠｡ んっ…
おっかしなこと言わないでよ｡
You're right, Master.
Don't be crazy.
悪ぃ 悪ぃ｡
Sorry, sorry.
≫(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)邪魔だ どけ｡
(２人)ん？
Get out of the way.
Oh, it's you.
おお～ おめぇ
朝から どこ行ってたんだ？
Where have you been?
Our group got a little bigger while you were gone.
お前がいない間に
仲間が増えたんだぜ｡
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)
俺は 貴様たちの仲間ではない｡
I am not part of your pathetic group.
Azazel, I'm glad you're okay.
アザゼル よかった 無事で｡
あ… あのときは
竜になれなくて ごめんなさい｡
I'm sorry that I couldn't turn into a dragon
when you needed me to.
私が あのとき…
あのとき 竜になっていれば…｡
If only I'd turned into a dragon then.
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)
貴様が竜になろうと なるまいと➡
It doesn't matter whether
you turn into a dragon or not.
関係ない｡
あっ｡
最初から期待などしていなかった｡
I never expected anything out of you.
パキン！
あっ アザゼル
ムガロちゃんも戻ってきたんだよ｡
Oh, Azazel.
Mugaro's back too.
ちょっと
前より成長しちゃってるけど➡
He's a bit more grown up, but you should
still be able to recognize him.
分かるでしょ？ って… あっ｡
Didn't Azazel recognize you?
アザゼル 分かんなかったのかな｡
RAGE OF BAHAMUT
They are the same
and lose themselves
Cuz there are lots of roads to go
And the path suddenly seems rougher
I wanna walk straight ahead
Knock down another dream
Most broke before they ever came true
But walk this way
Get out of my way
Depends on the way you think it
To a yielding heart
the future, hope,
despair and worry all look all the same
So much that you'll turn down the truth
that lied to you that day
when you were prepared for it all.
You go your way, don't you?
But walk this way
Get out of my way
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)牢獄島の様子はどうだ？
How did the prison island look?
I was watching from the sky,
(ﾊﾝｻ)上空から見てましたけど
近づく隙は なクワァったですね｡
but there was no opening to get any closer.
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)街の方も
おめぇらが脱走したせいか➡
The city was full of soldiers, too,
maybe in response to your escape.
兵士だらけだ｡
へえ～ 二人とも
ちゃんと働いてたんだね｡
Wow, you two were actually working for a change.
(ﾘﾀ)遊んでたのは
あなたとアフロとアザゼルだけよ｡
The only people who were playing around
were you, Afro, and Azazel.
すいません｡
やはり 腕輪の情報が➡
Sorry.
Is the intel on the bracelet really our only lead?
唯一の手がかりか｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)そもそも 王様は➡
Do we even know if the king
always has the bracelet on?
その腕輪を
常に着けているんですクワァね？
腕輪は
いつも着けているみたいだよ｡
It seems like he always has the bracelet on.
なんで あなたが知ってるの？
えっ？ え～っと…➡
How do you know that?
Oh, because I think he had it on
when I ran into him at the prison.
前 牢獄で会ったときに
してた気がしたから… あははっ｡
Even if that's true,
それが本当だとしてもよ
今 王様に近づくのは➡
how are we supposed to even get near the king?
無理がねぇか？
(ﾘﾀ)４日後➡
There's going to be a ball at the palace in four days.
王宮で舞踏会が開かれるわ｡
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)本当か？
Is that true?
(ﾘﾀ)貴族の元患者からの
情報だから 確かよ｡
I heard it from a former patient who's a noble.
It's reliable.
リタって 貴族も診てたんだね｡
I didn't know you treated nobles too.
I'll treat anybody as long as they pay me.
お金しだいで 誰でも診るわ｡
その舞踏会を狙って
王に接近するか｡
Should we try to move in on the king at the ball?
潜入するにしても
協力者が必要ね｡
We'll need help if we're
going to sneak into the ball.
What about your former patient?
リタの元患者は？
あれは三下貴族だから➡
He's from a third-rate family.
No way he's getting an invitation.
招待されないわ｡
三下かい｡
Well, that's no good.
私に任せてくれ｡
Please leave this to me.
Okay, then who is going to be the one sneaking in?
じゃあ 次は 誰が潜入するかね｡
はい！ よっと｡ 私が潜入して➡
Me!
I'll sneak into the ball
and steal the bracelet from the king.
王様から腕輪を奪います！
ん？ どした？
とっても不安ね｡
What's wrong?
It's not very reassuring.
(ﾊﾝｻ)お嬢さんは
もっと 暴れ回る役目の方が…｡
You're better suited for the
jobs where you can go wild.
大丈夫だって｡ 私 もう
好きなときに竜になれるんだから｡
It'll be fine. I've learned how to turn into a dragon
whenever I want to now.
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)うそをつくんじゃねぇ！➡
Stop lying. We're not playing around here.
遊びじゃねぇんだ｡
お前は出しゃばるな｡
Now stay out of it.
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ！
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)うわっ｡
ドォーン！
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ！
グルル…
(ﾘﾀ)どうやら… ごほっ
うそじゃないみたいね｡➡
It seems like she wasn't lying.
さっきも カイザルの隣にいて
平気だったし｡➡
I noticed she was fine being next to Kaisar too.
男にドキドキするのも
治ったのかしら？
Does that mean you no longer
get flustered around men?
グルル…
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ｡
See?
なぜ…➡
Why?
Why now?
なぜ 今更？
えっ？
ごめんなさい｡
愛されることを知ったから…｡
I'm sorry.
It's because I learned what it feels like to be loved.
(考古学者)ドロモスを
完全な出力で起動するには➡
We need 30 percent more energy
まだ３０％のエネルギーが
足りません｡
in order to activate Dromos at maximum output.
(ｼｬﾘｵｽ17世)すぐに完全にしろ｡
ですが 陛下 作業者たちに➡
Finish the task, then.
But, Your Majesty, the workers need to rest.
これ以上の負荷は…｡
褒美は 十分に与えている｡
They are being generously compensated.
あっ…｡
やれ｡
Do it.
Aye yai yai...
(隊長)陛下 私からも➡
Your Majesty.
May I give you my report as well?
報告をよろしいでしょうか｡
かまわん｡
Very well.
(隊長)昨夜 赤い竜の目撃情報が｡
We received word that the red dragon
was spotted last night.
堂々と アナティの上空を
飛んでいたとのことです｡
They say it was brazenly flying over Anatae.
茶番は やめろ｡
Enough of this charade.
我ら漆黒兵➡
We, the Onyx Soldiers,
全ての命は 王であるあなたに
ささげております｡➡
offer our lives to serve Your Majesty.
Please, give us the order.
どうか 使命の遂行に専念を｡
分かっている｡
I know.
The red dragon?
(隊長)赤い竜は？
(漆黒兵)行方は まだ｡
We have not located it yet.
必ず現れる｡ もう間もなくな｡
It will appear without fail.
It won't be long.
The man we've discussed will arrive tonight.
(漆黒兵)
例の男は 今晩 到着いたします｡
He's quick. Have the money ready.
早いな｡ 金を用意しておけ｡
(漆黒兵)御意｡
Yes sir.
Oh, hello.
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)あっ あの… どうも｡➡
ちょっと いいですか？
Could I have a moment?
Do not tolerate Charioce's arrogance!
You there, what are you doing?!
≪(兵士)おい 何をしている！
(男性)あっ｡ おい！
-Hey!
-Stop right there!
お… おう｡
(兵士)待て！
Stop!
待て～！
おい｡
Hey.
捜せ！
Find him.
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)((包帯悪魔と呼ばれる
賞金首は 俺だ｡➡
I'm the bounty being called the rag demon.
人間どもをおとしめ
魔族の失った誇りを取り戻す｡➡
I will slay the king of man and
take back the pride the demons have lost.
赤い竜を使う))
(ﾀﾞﾝﾃ)((俺たちは➡
I will use the red dragon.
All we can do is trust you.
お前を ただ信じるしかない))
(ﾍﾞﾙﾌｪｺﾞｰﾙ)((アザゼル様➡
Azazel, what is it that you are looking upon?
何を見ておられるのですか？))
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)((未来だ))
The future.
≪(ｴﾙ)ごめんなさい｡
I'm sorry.
あのとき
助けられなくて ごめんなさい｡
I'm sorry I wasn't able to help you then.
お前も俺に謝るのか｡
You're apologizing to me as well?
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)
お前が謝ることなど 何もない｡
You have nothing to apologize for.
RAGE OF BAHAMUT
Come in. Right this way.
(ﾎﾞｰｲ)こちらです｡
How long are you going to be making that face?
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)いつまで
そんな顔してるんですか？➡
It's not like we come here every night.
毎晩 来てるわけじゃないんだし
いいじゃないですか｡➡
厳しい訓練と任務に励んでるのに
俺たちにゃ➡
We devote ourselves to our hard training and duties.
Are we not allowed any simple pleasures?
娯楽も許されないんですか？
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)そんなわけではない｡
Of course you are.
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)だったらいいでしょ｡
さっ 早く座って｡
Then come on.
Sit down. Make yourself comfortable.
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)
だが こんな姿を団長が見たら…｡
But if the captain saw us like this...
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)
はあ!? 見れるわけないでしょ！
What? How the hell would he do that!
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ] ♬～(店内BGM)
アレサンド？
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)見れるわけないでしょ｡
Alessand.
Of course he won't see us.
あの人は今 脱獄中ですよ？
He's too busy being a wanted fugitive.
(ｹﾙﾍﾞﾛｽ)どうも～！
今日も元気なケルちゃんだぞ｡➡
Hey, there.
Cerby is here to cheer you up.
｢ワン｣｡ ｢ワン｣｡
おお～ ケル子➡
Oh, Cerby, I've missed you so much.
会いたかったぜ｡
(ｹﾙﾍﾞﾛｽ)もう～ アレ君➡
Oh, Al.
最近 来ないから
ケル子は お怒りだぞ｡➡
You know I'm mad at you
for not coming by at all lately.
ガウガウ｡
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)ごめん…｡
Okay, okay! I'm sorry!
(ﾗﾐｱ)さっ 難しい顔してないで
楽しみましょ｡
Now, how about you try to relax and enjoy yourself?
ツンツンって… どう？
(ｹﾙﾍﾞﾛｽ)ガウガウ！
Come on, what do you say?
Oh, are you okay, Al?
(ｹﾙﾍﾞﾛｽ)あら～ アレ君 大丈夫？
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)((あっ あの… どうも))
Ah...
((ちょっと いいですか？))
Could I have a moment?
((あの… 俺…))
I...
((用があるなら 早く言え))
If you have something to say, say it already.
((お… 俺
漆黒兵部隊に入りたいんです))
I'd like to join the Onyx Soldiers.
((あっ 待ってください！))
Please wait.
((本気なんです｡ ｵﾙﾚｱﾝ騎士団じゃ
もうダメなんです))
I'm serious.
The Orleans Knights are done for.
((価値がない))
((えっ？ 価値？))
You are not worth it.
What? Worth?
((貴様には
隊に入れるほどの価値はない))
You are not worth adding to our squad.
(ｹﾙﾍﾞﾛｽ)あっ アレ君
彼 今日から入った新人君だよ｡
Oh, Al.
This is his first day with us today.
なんか お前 むかつく顔してんな｡
You've got a real annoying face.
はい？
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)｢はい？｣じゃねぇよ｡➡
-Excuse me?
-No, don't "excuse me."
You've gotta stop it with that face.
お前 その顔やめろよ！
おい！ うっ！
Hey.
やめろって言ってんだろ！
はい？
-I told you to stop.
-Excuse me?
ちっ！
バキッ！
(女性たち)きゃあ～！
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)何をする アレサンド｡
What are you doing, Alessand?
何？ なっ なんで…｡
うぐぐっ…➡
What?
Why are...
ぐっ！
ガシャン！
Why were you here in disguise?
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)なぜ
変装などして このような場所に？
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)お前たちに会いたかった｡
I wanted to see you.
So you must have known
that we frequent places like this.
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)我々が
このような店に通っていたことを➡
ご存じだったのですね｡
I'm your superior officer.
私は お前たちの上司だぞ｡
協力してほしいことがある｡
There's something I'd like your help with.
私にできることなら なんなりと｡
I would be happy to do whatever I can.
アレサンド
お前にも協力してほしい｡
Alessand.
I would like your help as well.
You know of the weapon
His Majesty used, don't you?
お前たちも 陛下が使用した
破壊兵器は知っているだろう？➡
陛下が あの力で
これ以上の争いを望むのなら➡
If His Majesty wishes to use its power
for further conflict,
then I would like to stop him.
私は それを止めたい｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)しかし どうやって？
But how?
The palace ball that will be held in three days.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)３日後に王宮で開かれる
舞踏会 そこに潜入する｡
I will infiltrate it.
そこで アレサンド➡
That is where, Alessand...
お前の力を借りたいのだ｡
I would like your help.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)舞踏会には
一部の貴族しか参加できない｡➡
Only select nobles may attend the ball.
名家である
ヴィスポンティ家のお前なら➡
Being from the great Visponti family,
that should be no trouble for you.
容易にできるだろう｡
Please, I need your help.
頼む 力を貸してくれ｡
-Alessand.
-No way.
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)アレサンド｡
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)嫌ですよ…｡
-What?
-I said, I don't want to.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)なんだ？
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)嫌だって言ったんですよ｡➡
なんで俺が そんなことに
協力しなきゃいけないんですか｡➡
Why do I have to help you, anyway?
あんた 自覚あるんすか？
反逆者で脱獄犯で➡
Do you have any idea what your situation is?
You're a traitor, a fugitive,
第一級犯罪者なんすよ｡
そんなヤツのお願い➡
and on the kingdom's most-wanted list.
Why would I do any favors for someone like that?
誰が聞くんすか！
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)アレサンド！
-Alessand.
-And you're no better, Dias.
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)ﾃﾞｨｱｽさんもﾃﾞｨｱｽさんですよ
なんで いつまでも➡
-How can you keep licking his boots?
-Enough.
こんな人に へこへこしてんすか！
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)お前！
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)俺たち この人のせいで
惨めな目に遭ってんのに➡
He ruined our lives.
なんで怒んないんすか！
Why aren't you mad?
I'm sorry.
すまなかった｡
今更 謝られたって遅いんすよ！
It's too late for apologies.
俺たちオルレアン騎士団が
失ったものは もう戻らない｡➡
The Orleans Knights can never
get back what we've lost.
俺たちは 価値のない人間に
成り下がったんだ！ あっ…｡
We've been reduced to being worthless!
You are not worthless.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)お前たちは
価値のない人間ではない｡
You are my prized subordinates.
私の自慢の部下だ｡
悪いのは 全て私だ｡ だが➡
I am fully to blame for everything.
However...
今回だけは
協力してほしい｡
This is something I desperately need your help with.
たとえ
この命を失おうとも➡
Even if I should lose my life,
私は 陛下の真意を
知りたいのだ｡
I must know His Majesty's intentions.
Please.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)頼む｡
あぁ～ 言っときますけど➡
Just so you know,
危ないことはしないですからね｡
I'm not doing anything dangerous.
ありがとう｡
Thank you.
なっ!? ちょっと…｡
ふふふっ｡
Hey.
What are you doing, Dias?
何なんすか ディアスさん｡
ちょっと やめてくださいよ｡
Stop it.
気持ち悪い！
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)何をてれてんだ｡➡
-You're grossing me out.
-What are you blushing for?
いいじゃないか｡
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)てれてないっすよ！
I'm not blushing.
好きだ～～‼
I love you!
≫好きだ～～！
クワッ？
うるさいですねぇ｡
≫好～き～だ～！
I love you!
はははっ 言っちゃった｡
-Oh, my goodness, I said it.
-What are you doing?
≫何してんだ？ お前｡
し… 師匠！
Master? What are you doing here?
なんでいるの？
I came to see what all this commotion was about.
お前が騒いでるから
何事かと思って 来たんだっつぅの｡
べ… 別に 何もないから
もう戻ってよ｡
It's nothing, so you can go back now.
それ 誰からもらった？
あっ これ？
Who gave you that?
This? What?
なっ！ 見ないでよ エッチ！
Don't look, pervert.
エッチって お前…｡
Pervert? What?
Hey, Nina.
なあ ニーナ➡
お前が
何を隠しててもかまわねぇが➡
I don't care what you're hiding.
Just make sure you think hard before you act.
よく考えて選択しろよ｡
ん？
The world is put together pretty carefully.
世の中ってのは
よく出来ててよぉ➡
何かを選ぶと 何かを失っちまう｡
When you choose one thing,
you lose something else.
だから 俺は
めんどくせぇそれを避けるために➡
That's why I decided to avoid all the nonsense,
自由気ままに
賞金稼ぎをしていたが…➡
and live my life as a bounty hunter,
free to do what I wanted.
But even then, there are times when
you have to make important decisions.
それでも 大事な選択を
しなきゃならねぇときは➡
来ちまうんだ｡
師匠？
Master?
Even now.
今も その選択が正しかったのか➡
Did I make the right decision?
I just don't know.
俺には分かんなくてな｡
だから お前は
後悔しねぇように しっかり選べ｡
That's why you need to decide well,
so you don't have any regrets later.
よく分かんないよ｡
I don't really get what you're saying.
シャリオスが好きなんだろ？
You love Charioce, don't you?
言えない｡
I can't say.
I see.
そっか｡
好きだ～～‼
I love you!
ちょっ… おい！
Hey, stop that, Master.
師匠 やめろよ！
はいはい｡
Okay, okay.
I love you!
好きだ～～‼
だあっ！ ほんと➡
や～め～ろ～よ｡
Stop that right now!
好きだ 好きだ！
うるさい うるさい！
I love you!
-Shut up! Shut up!
-Stop! Seriously! Stop!
やめろ！ マジ やめろ！ 危ねっ｡
落ちろ！
-Watch it! Come on!
-I'm pushing you off!
≫やめろ！
ほんとに うるさいですねぇ｡
They're so obnoxious.
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)ぐおぉ～…｡
クワッ！
As horrible as you are
I can't help but love you
Even while I waited
That is all I felt
Ephemeral lovers, both flawed and missing pieces
We have finally become one
in this miniature garden at the edge of sorrow
Can you hear my heart speaking?
Ah, I may no longer feel
that I want to go back in time
But there are feelings, feelings, feelings
I can only feel now
I want to run away with you, dancing
just like in a fairy tale
Don't tell me it will only be this once, darling
I am on the same ark
Sha-ra-ran-la, Sha-ra-ran-la
Yeah
Cinderella step
Sha-ra-ran-la, Sha-ra-ran-la
Yeah
Cinderella step
(隊長)よく来てくれた｡
I'm glad you came.
Do you have the money?
金は？
This is all?
少ないな｡ 額が違う｡
I asked for more.
今は半分｡
殺したのを確認できたら➡
Half for now.
We'll pay the rest when we've confirmed the kill.
残りを払う｡
ふふっ 用心深いことだな｡
I see you're taking extra precautions.
で その赤い竜は どこにいる？
So where is this red dragon?
ふん｡
This is El.
I bet you were wondering when I'll talk!
I was waiting for my moment to shine!
Next time on Rage of Bahamut:
Virgin Soul, "Shall We Dance?"
No one is going to comment on that?!
BAHA SOUL!!
Baha Baha Baha Soul.
Watch next time too!